vacationrentalplanners.com 2014-09-29

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Collection of information and it's protection

We collect information like email addresses or other personal information required for authentication of property owners. This information is either collected through email communication or a direct phone call. This information is strictly used for owner identification and future correspondences only. We do not get involved in any information selling processes. Privacy of the information is our first priority.

**Entire property details, photos and other information is provided by the property owners. HolidayRentals.com is not responsible for any data duplicacy or authenticity as it is owners copyright and their responsibilty.**

We also record IP address of the visitor for statistics and analytics purposes on the listing pages of our website.

Email Marketing & Messages

We do not entertain spamming and are strictly against it. All our email messages and promotions are either to our registered owners or people who have subscribed for our newsletter to receive such promotions. If you do not wish to receive emails or promotions from us, please contact SUPPORT or simply click on the Unsubscribe link on these email messages.

Security of Information

We understand the importance of financial information and other important information we collect and we take serious care of it. Any financial information we collect for a sale or transaction purpose is deleted from the file to avoid any misuse. All these transactions are carried through on secure server.

Surveys

We do feedback surveys from time to time and we request users to input their valuable comments on our services or their experience with us. The decision to answer the survey is solely with the user. User may or may not fill in the details depending on their discretion.

Telephone Calls

In addition to collecting data online, we may also speak to our users on phone. This can either be for customer support or any promotional marketing which we want to explain to our users. If you wish to unsubscribe from these calls, please contact us at SUPPORT or inform the telephone representative about the same. We follow strict DNC rules.

Rental Inquiries

Travelers send inquiries through email contact forms on listing pages. Once a traveler choose to send an inquiry, he/she should understand that the personal information filled in the form, like email, phone and other information, will be shared with the property owner. We request users not to enter any financial information like credit card numbers or bank account information in our email contact forms.

Phishing or False emails

If you receive an unsolicited email requesting personal information like credit card, bank account, date of birth or even your account credentials with us, please be informed that this must be from someone trying to gain access to your information unlawfully. We do not request for such information in emails. Please contact SUPPORT if you receive something like this.

Opting out of receiving marketing messages

As a part of marketing, we may contact you through email or phone.  
You can opt out of these marketing communications by following ways -: 

  * Contact us at SUPPORT
  * Click on UNSUBSCRIBE link on the email

Contact US

If you have any questions about our Terms & Conditions, Privacy Policy, Process of marketing etc, you may contact us at SUPPORT. 

Call our customer services team on the number below to speak to one of our advisors who will help you with all of your holiday needs.

Call: +44-121-318-5610
